The real world.
Real...
...of...
...fartions!
[music playing]
Cheers.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are the stars
of America's game.
It's Jack and Amanda White.
Spoking out here.
Thank you, Jim.
Thanks, everybody.
You're very kind, and we appreciate it.
We do.
Good bye.
See ya.
Hi.
Nice to see you all to show up.
We appreciate that.
Get ready for our first toss-up of the
night.
For $1,000, and the category is...
...place.
[music playing]
Stan.
United States Embassy.
That's it. Yes, sir.
[applause]
Stan Brown.
Lakewood, California, you just won
$1,000.
Let's see. You're retired, right?
I'm retired. 37 years in the oil and gas
industry, Pat.
Yeah. Enjoying life now, I guess.
Enjoying life, yes.
How about that?
Married for 38 years to my high school
sweetheart,
beautiful wife, Vicki.
We have two grown children, Joshua and
Allison.
And we have two grandchildren, KJ and
Tripp.
Oh, yeah, got 'em all in.
Got 'em for you.
You play golf now, these things?
I do play golf.
Yeah.
But I had a little story back.
I used to work at a golf course when
Tiger was five years old,
and we used to go out and play golf,
play rounds of golf with Tiger.
Tiger who?
Tiger Woods.
Oh, okay.
I don't know golf all that well.
Was he any good?
Yeah, he was.
That's a fine view of it.
Good to have you here.
Thank you.
Hi, Rita.
Rita Conley is from Brooklyn, New York.
Let's hear about life back in Brooklyn.
Yeah.
Start with your, start with family.
Well, I've been married to my super
husband,
Chateke, for 23 years,
and we have four children and one dog.
Okay, good.
What's this thing about giraffes you
have?
All past.
I didn't mean to get you all excited
there.
We don't have enough time to talk about
giraffes, Pat,
but I love them very much.
I love them.
It's never been easier to try out to be
a contestant on wheels.
Solve fun puzzles from the comfort of
your own home
with our brand new virtual auditions.
Apply today.
Graduate student Ash Caldwell walked
away with not one
collect vacation, but two.
You're going to Scotland.
Wow!
On their UK getaway, Ash and Mom Jill
discovered all the
treasures of Scotland.
Historic castles, bucolic countryside,
and the hustle and bustle of Edinburgh.
Plus a unique photo op with a local
shepherd.
Florence, Italy.
Wow!
On Collette's spotlight on Tuscany, Ash
explored the
iconic sights of Florence, Pisa and
Siena,
savoring the country's rich culture,
history and cuisine.
Now a seasoned traveler with Collette,
Ash appreciated his
expert tour guides who took care of all
the details.
Collette, the best in guided travel
since 1918.
(applause)
Love me some Collette.
Yes.
They're great to work with and we've had
some great trips.
Thanks to them over the years.
If you're traveling, they're the people
to use.
That sounded like a commercial, but it
was, it came from
what little heart I have.
Oh, you were quite hot.
Thank you very much.
You should see my liver.
We will see you, see you next time
before bye.
Bye.
Thanks, Collette.
(applause)
Puzzled about what to get your favorite
Wheel Watcher?
We've got the answer.
The options are endless with all new
apparel,
hats, drink wear and more.
Head to shopwheelafortune.com today.
(applause)
(music)
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ánh]