and the world.
Wheel of Fortune!
[audience applauding]
Cheers.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are the stars
of America's game.
That's City Tech and Vanna White.
Spelking out here.
Thank you, Jim.
Thanks, everybody.
You're very kind, and we appreciate it.
-Thank you. -Goodbye.
-See you.
-All right.
Nice of you all to show up.
We appreciate that.
Get ready for our first toss-up of the
night.
It's worth $1,000, and the category is
Place.
[swooshing]
[bell ringing]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[bell ringing]
Stan.
-United States Embassy.
-That's it, yes, sir.
[audience applauding]
Stan Brown, Lakewood, California.
You just won $1,000.
Let's see, let's start.
You're retired, right?
-I'm retired. 37 years in the oil and
gas industry, Pat.
-Yeah, and enjoying life now, I guess.
-Enjoying life, yes. -With your family.
Talk about that.
-I've been married for 38 years to my
high school sweetheart,
beautiful wife, Vicki.
We have two grown children, Joshua and
Allison,
and we have two grandchildren, KJ and
Tripp.
-Oh, you got them all in.
Good for you.
You play golf now, do you, Stan?
-I do play golf.
But I had a little story back.
I used to work at a golf course when
Tiger was five years old,
and we used to go out and play golf,
play rounds of golf with Tiger.
-Tiger who? -Tiger Woods.
-Oh, okay. -Tiger Woods.
-I don't know golf all that well.
Was he any good?
-Yeah, he beat me. -Okay.
-As a five-year-old.
-Good to have you here. -Thank you.
-Hi, Rita.
Rita Conley is from Brooklyn, New York.
Let's hear about life back in Brooklyn.
Start with your family.
-Well, I've been married to my super
husband,
Shatik, for 23 years,
and we have four children and one dog.
-Okay, good.
What's this thing about giraffes you
have?
-Oh, Pat, we don't have enough--
-I didn't mean to get y'all excited
there.
-We don't have enough time to talk about
giraffes, Pat,
but I love them very much.
Oh, goodness.
Did you know?
-Go ahead. -That the giraffes--
The dots on the giraffes are just like
our fingerprints,
that no two giraffes have the same.
-Really? -Yeah.
-So should a giraffe commit a crime,
it would be easy to track him down.
-We're gonna know who it is.
-We don't need NCI, whatever that is.
-No. -Right.
Well, maybe during the show,
we'll have some more fun facts about
them.
Good to have you here.
Hi, Trisha. -Hi, Pat.
-Trisha Skaglione, right? -That's right.
-Is from Plantation, Florida.
Doctor of audiology, it says here.
True? -That is true.
-Yep, and a married doctor of audiology.
-I am a married doctor.
I am married to my amazing husband,
Brett, of eight years.
He makes me laugh every day with his
puns and bad jokes.
-Oh, good. -And we have two cats,
Gus and Rellie.
-Now, you-- it's a good week for you to
be here
with Colette and all the travel,
because that's a big thing for you guys,
right?
-It is. I'm a big traveler.
I've been to over 30 countries
and looking to add more to the list.
-All right, well, we'll see how that
goes.
Get ready, everybody. We'll do another
toss-up.
This one is worth $2,000,
and the category is "Living Things."
[bell dings]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
-Anastan. -I mean, birds.
-Nope. Nobody else?
Rita. -Homing pigeons.
-Yeah, that's it.
[applause]
I was afraid you were gonna say "homing
giraffes."
Yeah, but you didn't do that. -I wanted
to, but...
-I know you were tempted.
Jim, what do you have? -Well, here's
tonight's
featured Colette vacation, Pat.
Travel with Colette and discover the
scenic beauty
of Utah's mighty five national parks.
Behold the incredible vistas and
sandstone sculptures
of Arches National Park, Bryce Canyon,
and Zion.
Take in the views at Canyonlands and
Capitol Reef.
Relax at a local winery and so much more.
Colette, travelers first since 1918.
Visit colette.com.
$8,800.
[cheers and applause]
All right, boys and girls, here we go.
Same letter is the category for this
round.
Every word in the puzzle starts with the
same letter.
An extra $1,000 when you figure out what
that is.
And Rita, you got that last toss-up.
You will spin first. -Sure.
-Here we go, Rita. -Here we go, Rita.
[applause]
-R, please.
-One R. It's worth $700.
[applause]
-I'd like to buy a vowel, please.
-Mm-hmm. -An "I."
-Okay, let's see. One "I."
[bell dings]
[drum roll]
$650. -N.
-There we go. One "N."
[bell dings]
-I'd like to buy an "E."
-There's an "E," yeah.
Boy, just things kind of scattered up
there, aren't they?
-Can I buy an "A"?
-Yes, one "A."
[bell dings]
[drum roll]
-What for an "M"?
-That's a good thing to go for.
There are three of them,
and they are in fact the same letter.
So you're gonna pick up that wild card
first,
and you get $500 for each of the "M's,"
and we throw an extra $1,000 in,
and when the dust settles, you have
$3,100.
What do you want to do?
[drum roll]
-$600. -D, please.
-No. [buzzer]
Trisha.
[drum roll]
-C.
-Uh-huh, four "C's."
[bell dings]
You have $3,200.
-I'd like to buy an "O."
-Oh, yeah, yeah, you'll get some "O's,"
a whole bunch of those, and...
Just about fixed things up for you here.
No vowels left.
And again, if you want to,
otherwise you're gonna solve it.
-I'd like to solve. -All right, go ahead.
-Monaco, Mexico, Morocco.
-Yeah, that's it.
Oh, oh, oh.
So you have the early lead with $2,950.
Good news is everybody has some money,
and we're just getting started.
We like it just that way.
We'll be right back.
-Tonight, "Show You the World"
is brought to you by the following.
-If your dog suffers from fear of
thunder,
fireworks, separation, or any other
anxieties,
ThunderShirt may be the answer.
-ThunderShirt absolutely, 100% works.
-Like swaddling an infant,
ThunderShirt applies constant, gentle
pressure
to a dog or cat's torso.
Available at these and other retailers.
Buy now before July 4th.
♪♪
-Tonight's Mystery Round is brought to
you by
Jackpot Party, the number one app
for the best three Vegas slots.
Download for free on the App Store or
Google Play
for a huge 45 million coin welcome bonus.
There's no party like a Jackpot Party.
$10,000.
[audience applauding]
-All right, "thing" is the category this
time, everybody.
There's a quick look at the puzzle.
And, Trisha, your turn to start.
-Here we go, Trisha. -All right, Trisha.
[audience applauding]
-And it's $850.
-T.
-There are two T's, which would be
$1,700 worth of T.
[audience applauding]
-I'd like to buy a vowel. -Okay.
-E.
-And here come three E's for you.
[audience applauding]
-I'd like to buy the A.
-Let's see, can we do that? Yeah, I
think so.
There's one A and there's two A's, and
that's it.
[audience applauding]
-$900. -N.
-A whole bunch of N's, and you're gonna
get $900 for each one.
One, two, three, four, five, six N's.
That adds up to $6,600.
-I'd like to buy the I.
-Yeah, two I's.
[audience applauding]
-I'll buy the O.
-You got it, three O's.
No more vowels.
Spin it or solve it. What do you think?
-Solve it. -Okay.
-International phenomenon. -That's
right, yeah.
[audience applauding]
I've always had trouble saying
phenomenon-mon-mon-mon-mon-mon.
$6,100 that round.
Now you have a nice lead with $9,050.
Congratulations.
But we have a prize puzzle coming up.
That's gonna impact somebody's score in
a big way.
Come back, see the back.
We're looking for a phrase this time in
our prize puzzle round.
And Stan will be the first spinner.
-All right, here we go.
[audience applauding]
-$500. -S.
-Yes, we have S's. Well, A-S and S.
[audience applauding]
Uh, no. Ooh, $900.
-T. -One T.
[audience applauding]
-I would like to buy an E.
-Oh, give him some E's, Vanna.
[audience applauding]
-$500. -About an H.
-Well, that's okay with me, except there
is no H.
So, Rita, it's your turn.
[audience applauding]
-$600. -I'm gonna try this Y.
Y.
-Well, if you say it one more time,
you'll be right.
There are three of them.
[audience applauding]
-$600. -R.
-One R. Yeah, you have $2400.
-Can I buy an A?
-There is no A. I'm sorry, Trisha.
-It's worth a shot. -Can I solve?
-Well, we'll know in a moment, won't we?
Go ahead.
-You won't believe your eyes. -That's
it, yeah.
[audience applauding]
So, you let them do the work, you solve
the puzzle,
and you're the one going to Croatia.
Listen to this.
-Here comes a slice of true European
luxury.
Travel with Colette and step into a mix
of scenery,
culture, and history in vibrant Croatia.
From Dubrovnik's iconic city walls
and ancient Diocletian's palace,
to beautiful Plivice Lakes National Park,
discover all this paradise on the
Adriatic has to offer.
Colette, travelers first since 1918.
Visit colette.com.
$10,100.
-Oh. I'm guessing your 30 countries
now becomes 31 with that. Very nice.
You're up to $19,150.
Congratulations, but don't give up
anybody.
We got lots more to give away.
We'll start with a triple toss-up when
we come back.
[audience applauding]
-Close captioning sponsored by...
-You did it! You won!
-Love game shows?
-I'm being printed!
-Well, Game Show Network is the home of
more new,
original game shows than any network
on...
-It's triple toss-up time.
Person is the category for all three of
these puzzles.
You've won worth $2,000.
Here we go.
♪♪♪
Stan.
-Direct Supervisors.
-Yes, sir.
That total looks a little better now.
Up to $3,000.
Let's try another one.
[dinging]
♪♪♪
Trisha.
-Middle Manager.
-Yeah.
[dinging]
That leaves one to go, and here it comes.
♪♪♪
Trisha.
-Tear Person.
-Yeah, she gets two of the three.
♪♪♪
Up to $23,000.
On the map is the category for this next
round,
and Trisha, you won the right to start.
[dinging]
$650.
-T.
-There are some T's, yes.
[dinging]
-May I have an E?
-Three E's.
[dinging]
-$500.
-H.
-Two H's.
[dinging]
-$500.
-N.
-I thought you might say that.
Yes, there are two N's.
Let them come up.
$3,050.
What do you want to do?
-I'd like to solve.
-Okay.
-The Netherlands.
-Yeah, she's on a roll, that's for sure.
$26,200 she has, thanks to that $3,000
plus she just won.
But the good news for everybody is we
have time for another round.
And here's another puzzle.
Food and drink, the category.
There it is.
And time's running a little short.
Stan, it's your turn to start, so it'll
be a final spin.
[buzzer]
We'll add a thousand, see what counts,
and this will be worth, on our Speed Up
Round,
will be $1,700.
Again, it's food and drink.
Stan, we start with you.
Let's have a letter, please.
-R.
-Yes, one R.
I don't think you'll solve it yet,
but we'll give you three seconds.
[buzzer]
Rita.
-N.
-No N.
Trisha.
-T.
-No T, Stan.
-C.
-Yeah, two C's.
Food and drink.
[buzzer]
Rita.
-H.
-No, Trisha.
-M.
-Two M's.
Three seconds.
[buzzer]
Stan.
-L.
-One L.
[buzzer]
-Y.
-Mm-hmm.
Food and drink.
[buzzer]
Trisha.
-E.
-No money for vowels, as you know,
but you're gonna get two of them,
and when Van is out of there,
you will have three seconds.
[buzzer]
Stan.
-B.
-Uh, there is your answer.
There is no B.
Rita.
-A.
-Three A's.
[buzzer]
-I did.
-Trisha.
-G.
-Yeah, there's a G.
What do we have there?
-Creamy guacamole.
-Yeah, that's it.
[applause]
-Hi. -How you doing?
Congratulations.
Boy, you are hot tonight.
$5,100 at round.
Our big winner, $31,300.
I'll be back to discuss things.
Funny how that word wants to come out at
the end.
It was really fun having you here.
I hope you had a good time.
-Thank you. I appreciate it.
-Send us some more fun giraffe facts,
okay?
-Yes, I will.
-Thanks, Rita, very much.
Stan?
-Thanks, Pat.
-Pretty good night, huh?
$3,000 for you.
We thank you very much for being here.
-Thank you.
-We thank you both,
and we'll move back here
and find out what you're gonna do
in the bonus round here
in terms of categories.
What are you doing, thing and phrase?
-Phrase.
-Hmm.
I think I'm gonna do the phrase question.
We'll be back, see how that works out in
just a minute.
-So, who's here with you?
-My husband, Brett.
-How you doing?
Oh, he has a good wave.
-He does.
-Are you ready to spin this wheel?
-I am.
-All right, go ahead.
She already has $31,300.
Would like more?
[audience applauding]
It appears to be stopping on the "S."
I'll take that and ask you to follow me,
please.
There's your spot.
All right, you chose phrase as your
category.
R-S-T-L-N-E.
We'll start you off with those letters.
Ask our audience to be very quiet as we
go through this.
Okay, three more consonants, one more
vowel.
M-F-D.
-And a vowel.
-O.
-All right.
Well, you get one full word.
A lot of help there, but you get some
other help.
Maybe she can do it.
All right, it's a phrase.
You have 10 seconds to try to talk it
out.
Good luck.
-I'm interested for motion.
I'm interested for potion, for motion,
for...
[upbeat music]
-Well, it's action and it's poised for
action there.
That was a tough one, it seems to me.
And we couldn't do the cash.
I wish we could.
She's going to Croatia.
She has $31,300.
And I think she's happy.
-I am.
-Thanks, Richard, very much.
-Thank you.
-Nice to have you here.
-It depends how you write that.
Who knows where in the world we'll be?
[audience applauding]
-It's never been easier to try out to be
a contestant on Wheel.
Solve fun puzzles from the comfort of
your own home
with our brand new virtual auditions.
Apply today.
-Graduate student Ash Colwell walked away
with not one Colette vacation, but two.
-You're going to Scotland?
-Wow.
-On their UK getaway, Ash and mom Jill
discovered all the treasures of Scotland,
historic castles, bucolic countrysides,
and the hustle and bustle of Edinburgh.
Plus a unique photo op with a local
shepherd.
Florence, Italy.
-Wow.
-On Colette's spotlight on Tuscany,
Ash explored the iconic sights of
Florence,
Pisa, and Siena,
savoring the country's rich culture,
history, and cuisine.
Now a seasoned traveler with Colette,
Ash appreciated his expert tour guides
who took care of all the details.
-Colette, the best in guided travel
since 1918.
[audience applauding]
-Love me some Colette.
-Yes.
-They're great to work with,
and we've had some great trips thanks to
them over the years.
If you're traveling, they're the people
to use.
That sounded like a commercial,
but it came from what little heart I
have.
-Oh, you have a great heart.
-Thank you very much. You should see my
liver.
We will see you next time.
-For more, bye. -Bye.
-Thanks, Colette.
[audience applauding]
Puzzled about what to get your favorite
Wheel Watcher?
We've got the answer.
The options are endless,
with all new apparel, hats, drinkware,
and more.
Head to shopwheeloffortune.com today.
[audience applauding]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
(upbeat music)
안
경